hey guys welcome back to my channel I'm
on my way to Walmart um I've been
needing a new straightener so I'm going
to try and find the best one and I'm
going to do a review um my mom is
driving crazy you want to see you say hi
Mom
hi look at her she's a good driver she
didn't take her eyes off the road I
don't look rough but oh well it's my day
off so as we're fixing to go to Walmart
and there's two straighteners that I
want to try I guess I'll just choose
whichever one looks
better if it's a better price
but I forgot what I was going to
say yeah so for today I'm going to be
doing a straightener review from the
drugstore hopefully I get a new one or a
good one because I need a new one but I
didn't feel like spending a lot of money
on one because I hardly use a
straightener
anyways but I needed something I needed
one
and I want to spend less than $50
so
yeah here we
[Music]
go my mom's a crazy driver she hit every
single bump on the way here
yeah we are here at
Walmart slow down s so exciting we're
going to Walmart
wohoo that's all there is to do in this
small town this is where all the social
Gatherings
happen glowing today besides this
pimple pimple I said I'm glowing today
besides this pimple on my face like my
skin looks good other than the
pimple my pimples the sides of the
Walmart oh no there's no GL there's no
oh there they
are right
there thank you you
too wear your mask peeps
here we are in the
straighteners I don't see any of the two
that I was thinking about
getting I want one that's good for
curling also
I think the one that I there was another
one I was looking into was a Remington
but they don't have
it oh I need some Clippers do they have
seniors
here no they don't have no seniors they
wouldn't have them at Walmart would
they so I found this one and I think
this is the one I'm going to go with cuz
and it's only
252 I guess I can return it if it's no
good
I will take this
one this was the straightener that I
decided to go
with this is the Remington pro
professional Pearl
ceramic 1 in flat iron I really wanted
to get the
heritage straightener and do a review on
it because I didn't really see I think I
only saw two reviews on YouTube and I
feel like I should have gotten it but
the thing with that is I think it only
has like four temperature settings so it
goes from
like uh maybe like 260 to 300 to 360 to
420 and there's like no in between and I
like to have a little more control but
part of me feels like I should have
gotten it to review it if I didn't like
it I could have returned it but anyway
any this is the one I ended up with it
says it has 1in floating plates for
smooth Glide 450 salon High Heats
digital controls with nine heat plus
settings auto shut off uh heats up in 50
seconds digital oh I already read that
temperature lock Salon length swivel
cord I can't I can't speak I paid $25
for it and I said I wanted to keep it
under 50 so I went well beyond well
below my budget I'm going to open it I
can't open this give me a minute so I
finally got this
open let's
see this is all it comes with in the Box
almost almost dropped
it I needed a new straightener big time
because the one I have there's like a
big I should show you guys but I kind of
don't want to get up right now to grab
it but it has like a break in the side
so it's really snagging my hair and
damaging it even more so this is the
[Music]
straightener it has the the buttons on
this
side this has like a little digital
screen it kind of
feels let's see I know it's not on it's
not plugged in but it feels like it'll
Glide nicely and
[Music]
curl all
right let's test this baby so the first
thing um I would say about about this is
it definitely doesn't
feel like really good quality but um oh
my gosh I turned it on for a
second like right after I plugged it in
I thought I was recording but then I
turned it right off and it's already hot
so it does get hot really
fast so okay so I was going to say it
feel it doesn't feel quality I guess
it's not bad these plates are did I say
they're ceramic plates
which I think the straightener that I
had before were yeah they're Pearl these
are Pearl ceramic pink beautiful
sany the straightener I had before the
plates
were titanium I believe but it still
damaged my hair feel like any heat you
put on your hair is going to damage your
hair no matter what you're using I am
sorry that I'm always in these videos
looking rough you know I'm so
comfortable with myself and I'm
comfortable with y'all and I know the
real ones will love me no matter what I
look like okay so buttons I really you
know I didn't notice the pink and I love
this this is like one of my favorite
tones of
pink I love it so there's the power
button okay so this is
20 20°
increments three let's do
320 just cuz that'll have heat
protectant yeah it it gets hot really
really fast like super
fast so the straightener that I had
before oh it's done y'all it's done does
it has temperature
lock whatever that
means oh it locks clo you can lock it
Clos there's like a
little thing in the back can you see
that I can't see it so I'm hoping y'all
can see it
like a
little yeah that's cool I guess for
travel um so I don't have to wrap my
cord around it to keep it closed how do
you do the temperature lock
maybe oh yeah okay
so whatever it's on you just hold it
down and then it
locks okay hey we're going to we're
going to finally straighten some hair I
just like section it in two separate the
top from the bottom because I have such
thin
hair I don't have much hair at all
so okay I'll just I'll kind of make this
neat just for you guys see my natural
hair is
wavy when I was living in Austin my hair
would get curly like it was beautiful
the humidity in the air would make my
hair so gorgeous
but I have been heat styling my hair a
lot
lately so it doesn't get
as as curled as it used
to oh okay so it already pulled my
hair it's pretty though
[Music]
H maybe I should turn it up I'm going to
do I'll do three I'll do 360 okay I
usually have it to like 400 and it gets
my hair like pin straight right away but
I'm not going to do
that this gets
hot like my hair was really hot I'm just
going to go ahead and do this whole
quadrant right here that I
have ow see it
pulls I don't know what it is that it's
pulling my hair
but H oh see I don't know how I feel
about this hold
on is it me am I just being kind of
like sloppy with it okay my hair is
shiny
it didn't really take that long to
straighten this whole part right here
I'm just kind
of okay okay okay let's see hair's long
see I don't know about the ends it's not
like getting my
ends the way I want it to yeah my hair
is really
shiny it gets it straight enough so I
think that this may be good for now
I had that undercut I don't know I never
showed it here on YouTube but I have
pictures of it on my Instagram but
before I graduated barber
school I got an undercut and it's
finally grown back out I don't know if
you guys can see it my hair's
short but okay
so let's see what a curl looks like on
this side of my head because I feel like
they come out better on this side
yeah I don't like I guess I think it's
the position that I'm holding my
straightener on this side but yeah it
does good
curls okay I'm just going to go ahead
and do the rest of my hair and then I
will check back in with you guys
so I did want to mention that I had to
go over all of my
hair like two times cuz I started with a
low setting I think I started at 360 and
I ended up at 400 or 420 if I would have
just started with a higher temperature I
probably wouldn't have had to go over it
as many times and things would have been
a lot
smoother also a few days after filming
this I curled all of my hair with with
the straightener I don't have the
footage I wish I would have gotten some
footage to
show but the curls lasted a good 3 Days
by the time by the third day there were
waves but it was still really nice just
threw in some dry shampoo and my hair
was good to go for a good 3
days so yes I hope you guys enjoy the
rest of this video
this is my hair after it's all been
straightened it's really shiny and it
looks
healthy um at when I had it
at 360 is that what I had it at yeah it
was like snagging my hair a little bit I
turned it up a little to 390 it started
gliding through my hair a little easier
and I feel
like it got it a little more more
straight but yeah it was I think it's I
think it's good enough to do the job um
like I said it was only $25 so see let
me make
sure have the
receipt yeah
2512 so that's not bad
um I don't straighten my hair that often
I usually just wear it naturally but I
guess it is good for when I want to curl
my hair cuz I really do love curling my
hair with the
straightener so it worked on
that my hair is
decent it looks good so I think I'm
going to keep it overall this was a
really good straightener
for
cheap the Remington Pearl I can can see
why they put the little temperature lock
in it to it because whenever I was
straightening my hair my hand was
pushing the buttons overall this was a
good
product turn it off need hold the power
button
down good product 25 bucks it's going to
do the job for me all these little
flyaways look crazy I wish I had my
leaving conditioner right here but oh
one thing I was going to say about this
is it leave it left like a dent right
here like it's really hard to get at the
root
but maybe it was the way I was doing it
I was kind of rushing through and if I
would have sectioned my hair like like
this and then kind of took the time
to it may not have left the dent with
these flyaways I usually just get some
leave-in conditioner
and yeah that is it for today's video I
just wanted to kind of review and see if
I could find like a decent straightener
at the drugstore
and I think I did okay um it's I think
it'll work really well if you have like
a hair texture like mine like very thin
fine hair I didn't know what I was
getting until I got there as you guys
saw this is all I need I can get rid of
my old one that thing is old and it's
just prying my my the crap out of my
hair so
yes I don't know what else to say I
think I think that's a
wrap I better stop before I B my face
but that is it for this video guys thank
you so much for watching as always
wishing you peace and don't forget to
love
yourself catch you in the next one bye
m